Freddy Krueger : My children ...
From the very beginning ...
It was the children who gave me my power .
The Springwood slasher ...
That 's what they called me .
[ Blades spring out ]
[ Girl screams ]
My reign of terror was legendary .
Dozens of children would fall by my blades .
[ Laughs ]
Then the parents of Springwood came for me ...
Taking justice into their own hands .
When I was alive , I might have been a little naughty ...
But after they killed me ,
I became something much , much worse- -
the stuff nightmares are made of .
The children still feared me ,
and their fear gave me the power to invade their dreams .
And that 's when the fun really began !
Aah !
Until they figured out a way to forget about me !
To erase me completely !
Being dead wasn 't a problem .
But being forgotten- - now , that 's a bitch !
Aah !
It 's only a dream !
Die , motherfucker !
Freddy : I can 't come back if nobody remembers me !
I can 't come back ...
If nobody 's afraid !
I had to search the bowels of hell ...
But I found someone ...
Someone who 'll make ' em remember .
He may get the blood , but I 'll get the glory .
And that fear is my ticket home .
Mike ?
Is that you ?
All right , fuck you , then .
I 'm heading in .
Mike ?
Come on , it 's not funny anymore .
Ohh-aaah-aaah , aaah !
Aah !
[ Whimpering ]
[ Gasping ]
Ohh ... Oh ...
[ Wood creaks ]
No !
Jason 's mother : Jason .
I should 've been watching them , not drinking .
Not meeting a boy at the lake .
I deserve to be punished .
We all deserved to be punished .
Jason 's mother : Jason .
My special , special boy .
Do you know what your gift is ?
No matter what they do to you ,
you cannot die .
You can never die .
You 've just been sleeping , honey .
But now the time has come to wake up .
Mommy has something she wants you to do .
I need you to go to elm street .
The children have been very bad on elm street .
Rise up , Jason !
Your work isn 't finished !
Hear my voice and live again !
Make them remember me , Jason .
Make them remember what fear tastes like .
Ha ha ha ha ha ha .
I 've been away from my children for far too long .
[ Freddy cackles ]
[ Hard rock music playing ]
[ Thunder ]
Marry , fuck , or kill ? Your choices are- -
your choices are the 3 stooges .
Go , Kia .
Oh , God ...
Uh , which one had the super bad toupee hair ?
Harry , moe- -
no ! No , no , no . It was moe .
Either one , I 'd kill him .
Ok , who 'd you fuck then ?
This is stupid , y 'all .
Come on . Come on .
Oh , God . Whatever , look .
I 'd fuck the bald guy , and I 'd marry Larry .
Jesus . Is this what we 're doing all night ?
'Cause , y 'all , this is really stank .
Hey ! Gibb , what are you doing ?
I thought you were gonna quit ?
I only smoke when I drink now .
But you 're always drinking .
Yeah , well , I 'll work on that next .
Hey , ok .
I got another one .
Fred , Scooby ,
or shaggy .
Oh ! I 'm not answering that ,
and neither is she .
Do you guys think I should get a nose job ?
Oh , my God .
Oh , please , Kia ,
what you need is a lobotomy .
I think I 'm gonna get some candles .
I 'm gonna get some beer . You guys want anything ?
Are you sure you should be driving ?
I 'm so under the limit , Lori .
Surprise .
Oh , Trey . You answered my prayers .
Thank you .
Whoa , babe !
What 'd I tell you about kissing me
after you smoked , huh ?
Lighten up . They 're menthols .
Yeah . I brought Blake . Where 's Linda ?
It 's Lori . This is her house ,
so don 't be a total cocksmith .
Whatever .
Where are the ladies ?
Relax , they 'll be here .
I 'm relaxed , man . I 'm just wet .
Did you know they were coming over ?
[ Softly ] Listen , you gotta be quiet .
Hey , we knew you were be here all alone this weekend .
[ Sighs ]
Blake 's cute .
[ Softly ] He 's not my type .
Oh ! Who is ? No one 's ever gonna live up
to the fuzzy memory of your first love , Lori .
You were fucking 14 , so get over it .
Yeah , I know we were young ,
but what will and I had was real .
Well , correct me if I 'm wrong ,
but didn 't Mr. real just drop-kick your ass
without so much as a good-bye handshake ?
He ever even call
or maybe even write to you after he moved ?
Send you an e-mail ?
No .
You see my point ?
It 's time to leave the convent , Lori .
You need to meet a guy .
[ Sighs ]
Uhh .
[ Thunder ]
[ Rb music playing ]
Blake : Hey , Lori ,
I , uh , I like the ...
Flow of your place . Got good feng shui .
Yeah .
You know about feng shui ?
Oh , oh !
Oh , you should see her bedroom !
Hmm ? Great flow in there .
Lori , why don 't you go upstairs
and show Blake your feng shui .
Shut up !
[ Thunder rumbles ]
I got a kink in my neck .
Come on . You can massage it out for me .
I think I need a few more drinks
before there 'll be any massaging .
What do you see in him ?
[ Whispering ] I don 't know , but he has a cute ass .
Babe , don 't make me ask you twice , ok ?
So , Lori ...
Am I gonna get that grand tour or what ?
Yeah .
You know , why don 't you start in the kitchen ,
and get us some beers .
Cool .
Oh , my God , Kia , he is a total idiot .
Get him out of here .
Oh , Lori , come on , give him a chance .
I don 't like him .
You know what ? You don 't like anybody .
I mean , Lori , you 've barely gone out since- -
since what ? Since my mom died ?
Yeah , well , you know what ? My dad needs me .
So I can 't just go out with guys all the time ,
and if I did , it would not be with somebody like Blake .
[ Wind howling ]
[ Floorboards creaking ]
[ Gibb breathing heavily ]
Trey : Yeah , fuck me , baby !
Aah ! Aah !
Your back door was open .
I closed it .
Mm .
Babe , you know I don 't like
to be touched after , ok ?
Fine . I 'll go have a shower then .
Good .
Your hair smells like menthols , anyway .
Asshole .
Ahh .
[ Shower running ]
Ohh !
Aah !
Unh ! Aah ! Ack !
Trey !
What the hell are you doing ?
Aah !
[ All screaming ]
Help us ! Help us !
Oh , my God !
Over here !
Please help us !
Help us !
You kids need some assistance ?
What the fuck do you think ? !
We need to lock this down now .
Keep it contained , you hear me ?
Killed in bed .
Jesus .
It 's even the same damn house .
1428 elm .
It 's gotta be him , right ?
It 's gotta be Freddy Krueger .
Hey ! Don 't even say
that son of a bitch 's name out loud .
Let 's just keep it together .
We 've been through too much
to let this thing spread now .
Take all the kids down to the station .
Keep them separate . Do it now .
Yes , sir .
We 'll be in touch .
Thank you . Let 's go home .
[ Huffs ]
So ?
She doesn 't know anything .
None of them do .
I 'm pretty sure we 're good .
Pretty sure ? You better make damn sure
none of those kids knows anything ,
or I 'll send your ass up to westin hills with them .
Knows what ? What do you mean ?
Good work there tonight , Stubbs .
Right place , right time .
But we 'll take it from here , all right ?
Your father 's on his way .
Do they know who did this ?
No , not yet .
But I thought I heard
one of the officers mention a name .
You know , to tell you the truth , Lori ,
I--I just moved here about a month ago ,
but if they have a suspect ,
I 'd be the first to know .
But they asked me all these really weird questions ,
like about my dreams- -
[ knock on glass ]
What was the name ?
Freddy .
[ Child sobbing ]
Hello ?
[ Sobbing ]
Are you ok ?
Ohh !
[ Various voices ] His name is Freddy Krueger .
And he loves children ,
especially little girls .
Freddy 's coming back .
Soon he 'll be strong enough .
It 's ok to be afraid .
We were all afraid .
Warn your friends . Warn everyone .
Aah !
Aah ! Ohh !
Children : ¶ 1 , 2 , Freddy 's coming for you ¶
¶ 3 , 4 , better lock the door ¶
¶ 5 , 6 , grab a crucifix
¶ 7 , 8 , try to stay up late ¶
¶ 9 , 10 , never sleep again
¶ 1 , 2 , Freddy 's coming for you ¶
aah ! Ohh !
Ohh .
Blake , we have to talk .
What the hell were you doing over there ?
You were supposed to be watching your sister .
Were you drinking ?
My best friend was just killed , dad !
So how about giving me
some fucking space .
You watch yourself , boy .
I 'm gonna get him for you , Trey .
Cop let it slip .
It was somebody named Freddy .
I 'm gonna take him out myself , Trey .
I swear to God .
[ Bushes rustling ]
Who is that ?
Someone there ?
[ Baa ] Ohh !
Jesus . [ Baa ]
Ha ha ha ha ha !
I 'm ok . I 'm all right .
Not strong enough yet .
Well , I will be soon enough .
Until then ... Heh heh heh !
I 'll let Jason have some fun .
Dad ?
Aah ! Aah !
Aah !
Hypnocil . What does this shit do , anyway ?
How come we all have to take it ?
It keeps you nice and docile
while I kick your little ass .
I 'm fine with that .
Announcer on TV : We interrupt this program
for a special report .
After tonight 's murder
in this neighborhood of Springwood ,
the sheriff 's department has confirmed
that there is one victim ...
Hey , turn that up , man .
Remain sketchy , but the sheriff- -
sorry , will . You know the rules .
Turn that back on . I know somebody
that lives in that house .
Come on , turn it back on , man !
I never ask for anything .
Just turn on the fucking TV , please !
Fuck you , man !
What the fuck is your problem ? !
What are you doing , man ?
You want 10cc 's of that pink
tranquilizer in your ass ?
That was Lori 's house .
They said something about a murder .
I gotta- - I gotta go to her .
I gotta see if she 's ok .
Back to Springwood ?
Do you want me to start having nightmares again ?
Don 't start with that dream demon shit again .
Ok ? You know that 's all just in your head .
Yeah , yeah , and who are you ,
the poster boy for sanity ?
You 're the one that told the cops
Lori 's dad killed his wife .
Yeah , right , and now it looks like someone else
got killed in the same house .
You think that 's a coincidence ?
2 murders in one house ?
Kurt , how many times do I have to tell you , man ?
I don 't do checkers .
I 'm an uno guy , all right ?
So go grab the fucking uno deck
and we 'll play , ok ? Please . Thank you .
Look at us , will .
Look around you , man .
We 're institutionalized .
We 're stuck here . We 're not going anywhere .
Mark : I do miss my family , man .
I mean , it 's been 4 years
since I 've seen ' em , you know .
All these years , and you 're still convinced
you saw her father do that ?
I know what I saw , mark .
Fuck what the doctors try
to get me to believe .
I need to know if she 's ok .
[ Howling like monkey ]
[ Farts ]
You want to play ?
Uhh .
Sweet dreams , monkey boy .
What the hell was that for , man ?
Heh heh heh !
You 're a fucking lunatic , you know that ?
I know you are , but what am I ?
Are you sure you didn 't see anyone ?
No , dad , none of us did .
I already went over this with the police .
It 's just ...
I don 't know what I 'd do without you .
You 're all I have left .
Dad , I 'm not going anywhere .
I promise .
Look at you .
You 're exhausted .
Freddy : Lori .
We need to get you to bed !
Ohh ! Oh ! Um ...
I don 't want to go to sleep , dad .
I just want to see my friends .
I don 't think it 's a good idea
for you to go to school today .
You 've just been through
a very traumatic experience .
Dad , please ...
I just need to get out of the house , ok ?
I 'll be fine . I promise .
Well , at least drink your juice .
Will rollins and the Davis boy
escaped from westin hills last night .
Oh , Jesus .
It 's all coming apart again .
Don 't worry . We 'll find them .
Keep this thing contained .
Kia : Lori !
Oh , my God ! God , you guys , I 'm so glad you 're here .
Uh , Blake 's dead , too .
What ?
Yeah , he- -
he was stabbed to death late last night .
Um , same with his dad .
What ?
Shit , shit ! This is bullshit !
The police are blaming
everything on Blake like its some kind
of columbine thing or something .
They 're saying he went crazy .
Killed Trey , killed his dad ,
and then took his own life ?
This is so fucking messed up .
This is messed up .
[ Bell rings ]
Excuse me . Sorry .
Uh , Lori ?
What is it , Linderman ?
Um , well , I heard what happened ,
and I just wanted to express how , um- -
well , to tell you how sorry I was .
Thank you . That 's sweet .
Right . You know , actually ,
if you need anybody to talk to or- -
whoa , Linderman , let me give you a tip .
Place your hormones back in the box
and quit while you 're ahead , ok ?
We don 't have time
for date-a-dork right now . Thanks .
Right . Uh , sorry .
I swear , every day it 's the same thing .
He 's like one of those fucking frou-frou dogs
that keeps humping your leg .
Give a couple to some ladies .
Thanks , man .
I see what you 're saying , Gibb ,
but that 's exactly why you should go .
I mean , be amongst friends
where it 's safe . There 's gonna be
a whole lot of loving there for you
and my boy Trey , all right ?
Yeah . Yeah , you 're right . I should go .
I could use a few dozen drinks .
That a girl .
Let your freak flag fly .
See you there .
You want to go ?
No , I don 't think so .
I--I didn 't get much sleep last night ,
and when I did sleep ,
I had the most terrible nightmares .
Lori , you had to sleep at a police station .
I 'd have nightmares , too .
No , no , no , it wasn 't like that .
I mean , this was really real .
I mean , there was this man ,
but he more like a monster really ,
and they kept calling him Freddy ,
and he was so real . Shh !
What did he look like ?
He--he had this ...
Dark brown hat , and ...
His skin was terribly burnt ,
and on this right hand he had this like these
razor fingers , and- -
Kia : You must be tripping .
No , no , no !
And then there were these little girls ...
It 's ok . It was a bad dream .
They were singing like this--this song like- -
¶ 1 , 2 , Freddy 's coming for you ¶
you know why they sing that ?
Because that 's when he comes for you ...
In your dreams .
You 're lucky to be alive .
Who is he ?
He 's a child murderer
that some parents from around here
burned alive , but then he came back .
Back for revenge in our nightmares .
Funny no one ever told us about him , huh ?
Ok , thank you ! No !
Want some free advice ?
Coffee . Make friends with it .
Will : Mark !
That 's enough .
You 're scaring her .
Will ?
Hey .
Uh ...
I thought you might be in trouble , so we- -
Lori ! Oh , my God !
Lori , honey , wake up !
Someone get help , please !
Someone get some help , please !
The principal ! Will , let 's go , let 's go !
Please , somebody help her . Lori ?
How much longer is it gonna take ?
Is she ok or what ? Shh .
Tsk !
For nose jobs , what kind of anesthesia
do the doctors use ? They put you
all the way under , right ?
Ohh !
Got your nose !
Aah !
Ohh !
Strong work , man .
I came to make sure she 's ok
and you put her in the infirmary .
What were you thinking about ,
telling her all that stuff , man ?
I mean , we 're not in group .
Because I 'm thinking for the first time
in my life that maybe I 'm not crazy ,
that my brother wasn 't crazy .
She had the same dream , will .
Officer : Will rollins ! Mark Davis !
[ Bell rings ]
Mark : This doesn 't make any sense .
There 's nothing on Krueger .
Not his arrest , his death ,
not even a birth certificate .
Whole sections of the records are gone .
Look at all these blacked-out obituaries .
January 18th . That 's the day
my brother committed suicide .
Why isn 't that in here ?
I don 't know !
But I 'm sure there 's a good reason .
I mean , remember in group when they told us
not to jump to conclusions .
Listen to yourself . You 're holding onto
that psychobabble bullshit
like it 's some kind of security blanket , man .
Let it go . They covered him up , will .
They never told us about Freddy
because that 's how they decided to beat him .
They treated him like he was a fucking disease ,
and they locked up all the kids
who had made contact with him
so they wouldn 't infect the others .
That 's crazy ? Is it ?
How come we were never allowed
to call any of our friends , man ?
How come none of our friends ever called us ?
We were in a fucking quarantine , man .
That 's what westin hills was for .
Will : Well , even if all you 're saying is true ,
then why didn 't Freddy kill Lori ?
Maybe he 's not strong enough yet .
My brother said it 's our fear
that gives him his power .
Yeah , well , you sure as hell
spread enough fear today at school .
Holy shit .
You 're right .
They wanted to forget Freddy
so they wouldn 't fear him- -
what if I screwed up the town 's plan ?
No .
Fuck ! This fucker 's gonna spread
like the plague , man . Kids are gonna start
falling asleep , it 's gonna- -
let 's leave , man , let 's leave right now .
No , I can 't leave .
Why not ?
I gotta go talk to Lori . I gotta see if she 's ok .
Well , is she worth dying for ?
Because if you fall asleep ,
you ain 't waking up .
Yeah , well , if that 's the case ,
how come you 're not dead ?
Or any of the freaks at westin , huh ?
When 's the last time you even had a nightmare ?
I don 't know .
I can 't remember my dreams anymore .
Look , just give me one night , ok ?
Just let me find Lori , and then we 're out of here .
I swear .
All right . If your ass isn 't back here
by dawn , I 'm gone . We clear on that ?
This baby 's my brother 's
pride and joy , so be careful .
[ Techno music playing ]
Oh , shit .
Linderman !
Uh , shack , I don 't drink .
[ All laughing ]
Hi , Lori . Didn 't think I 'd see you here .
Uh , can I get you something to drink ?
Smooth opening , but , you know ,
we 're already taken care of .
What happened to your clothes ?
Oh , this . Uh ...
I was playing a drinking game
with some of the , uh , lower primates ,
and I guess I 'm penalized for my ability
to read above a fourth grade level .
Linderman , you know , I always pictured you
as a straight up bed wetter .
You know what , Kia ?
I used to think you hated me
because you thought I wasn 't good enough for Lori ,
but that 's not it . You see , you tear me down
to make yourself feel better
because you really hate yourself ,
which is kind of pathetic when you actually
stop and think about it , assuming , of course ,
you can think with all that make-up
weighing down your head .
The cops said Blake committed suicide .
Apparently , it was grief over Trey .
No , man , that 's bullshit .
I heard some guy Krueger
killed them both .
Said his name to my parents ,
they almost shit themselves .
Yeah , yeah , yeah , man , and I heard
that Freddy freak , he used to live here .
Fucking gutted Trey like a goddamn Turkey , man .
Like I heard his intestines and shit
was on the floor- -
oh , shit . I 'm sorry .
Oh , my God .
Look who 's here . Look who 's here !
Kia : What are you looking at ?
Come on , come on , let 's dance .
Come on , Linderman , let 's go .
Where have you been , will ?
Didn 't you get my letters ?
What letters ?
They must 've never even mailed them . Heh !
Who ?
The ... Doctors at westin hills .
I 've been in a psychiatric hospital .
Uh , mark was with me there .
Some other kids , too .
I don 't understand .
Well , I saw on the news the other night ,
I mean , that kid that was killed at your house .
I mean , I needed to know that you were safe .
What happened ?
I don 't know . I don 't know .
Nobody knows . Nobody saw what happened ,
and the police have been acting
really weird , like they know something ,
and I heard them mention some name .
Some ...
Freddy . Freddy Krueger .
Where was your dad ?
Out of town .
Are you sure ?
What is going on , will ?
Well , look , 4 years ago , I thought I- -
Kia : Enough with this bullshit talk .
Let 's go shake our ass
on the dance floor . Come on !
Trey : I 'm dead one day
and you 're already out getting shit-faced ?
Same old Gibb !
Trey , I- - I can 't believe it- -
come on , let 's go .
Babe , don 't make me ask you twice , ok ?
Now !
Gibb : Trey ?
Trey ?
[ Softly ] Oh .
[ Water trickling ]
Trey ?
Trey !
Ohh !
Aah ! No !
Open the door !
Please , the door- -
aah !
[ Moans ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Hiss ] Ohh !
Aah !
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha !
No ! No !
Aah !
[ Clanking ]
[ Blades scratching metal ]
You 're the one that killed Trey !
Oh , don 't worry about my little errand boy .
The only to fear
is fear himself !
Aah !
Uhh !
Oh .
[ Groaning ]
[ Creaking ]
Aah ! Aah !
[ Gasping ]
Aah !
No !
She 's mine .
Mine ! Mine !
This everclear is kicking my ass .
This--ha ha ha !
Check out this fucking guy .
Well , hey , Jethro !
This is a rave , not a Halloween party .
Why don 't you go find yourself
a pig to fuck ?
Yeah !
Invite only , cornpoke .
And you weren 't invite- -
son of a bitch .
Uhh !
Yeah !
Burn , mother fucker !
Ohh !
[ Whimpering ] No !
Uhh !
[ Crowd screaming ]
Run , man , run !
[ Car engines starting ]
Aah !
Freak ! You killed my brother !
Whoa !
Gibb ! Oh , my God !
Oh , Gibb ! No !
Let 's go ! Let 's go , come on !
Was that him ?
The guy you were talking about ?
Freddy Krueger ?
No , that wasn 't the guy in my dream .
That was somebody else !
Who cares about some fucking dream guy , ok ?
That psycho in the hockey mask was real .
Dude , that goalie was pissed about something .
We need to find the police .
No , no ! Fuck the police !
Just take me home , will .
Gibb , I- -
I can 't believe she ...
I know .
[ Softly ] I know .
Look , call me later , ok ? Please ?
Just to check in .
Ok . [ Sniffles ]
Bye , will .
Be careful .
[ Thunder ]
Will , I 'm gonna go inside now .
No , I think that 's the last thing
you should do right now .
Oh , will , please .
After everything that 's happened ,
I just want to go to- -
there 's more to it than that .
Look , I tried to tell you this earlier .
The reason I was sent to westin
is because I saw your dad kill your mom .
Will , my mom died in a car accident .
No , that 's what he wanted you to believe ,
but I was there , Lori .
I was sneaking up to your room
like I used to do .
Only you weren 't there .
I saw him kill her .
[ Knocking ]
Dad !
Get out of the van .
Get out of the van ! Where were you ?
What are you doing ?
I 've been looking all over for you !
Get away from her !
You 're in a helluva lot of trouble ,
you know that ?
Yeah , like I give a shit anymore .
Get in the house !
You ! I 'm taking you back to westin .
No ! No way ! You can 't trust him , Lori .
Whatever you do , don 't go home with him !
No , listen to me !
Lori , he was the one who had me committed !
See , you didn 't understand .
You still don 't . You were confused !
Stop it !
Both of you , stop it !
Damn it , will ! I am not gonna
let you endanger my daughter again !
Not after everything that 's happened !
Stop it ! Stop it ! Fuck !
Lori !
[ Coughs ]
Lori ! Lori !
I--I- -
did mom die in a car accident ?
Yes . Of course she did .
Prove it .
Show me a death certificate .
Show me an autopsy report .
Lori , I don 't think now is the right time- -
really , dad ?
Because I think it 's a perfect time !
Why didn 't you tell me about westin hills ?
Do you work there ? Because I thought
you were a fucking general practitioner !
Yes , I ...
I do some consulting there now , but ...
It 's--it isn 't what you think .
Oh , my God .
So you knew about will this whole time .
Lori , listen to me .
You 're upset . We both are .
Now I think what you need now
more than anything is to get some rest .
Why don 't I give you some pills ,
and that 'll help you sleep ,
and then we talk about it in the morning ?
I don 't want to sleep , dad !
I want to know why you 've been lying to me !
We 'll talk about it in the morning !
Now do what I say !
Lori ! Lori !
Lori !
Open this door . Open this door !
Go away !
Dr. Campbell : Damn it , Lori !
Let me in !
Lori !
Goddamn it !
Aah !
It 's ok , it 's me . It 's me , shh ! Shh !
You ok ? Are you ok ?
It 's me , all right ?
Will : I don 't know how your father 's
connected to all this ,
but I think mark was right .
There 's some kind of cover-up
going on here with Krueger .
We can 't trust the police .
We can 't trust any of the adults .
So what do we do ?
We gotta get to mark .
He 's the expert in all of this .
He 'll know what 's going on .
[ Stereo playing ]
You always looked out for me , bro .
Man , ghostly : Hey , mark .
[ Water running ]
[ Whispering ] Just stay awake .
[ Sighs ]
Shit !
Hey , mark .
You didn 't forget about me , did you ?
Oh , God .
[ Freddy 's voice ] Oh , that 's right !
Everyone forgot !
That 's why they weren 't afraid anymore !
That 's why I needed Jason to kill for me
to get them to remember .
But now he just won 't stop ,
that hockey puck !
Aah !
Freddy : Ha ha ha !
Ha ha ha !
This isn 't ... Real .
[ Hissing ]
Somebody , please , wake me up !
Please !
[ Tires screeching ]
Mark ! Mark , wake up !
I need you to send a little message for me .
That 's all , just a little message .
Mark : I 'm not gonna do it .
I won 't do it !
No ? !
I won 't do it . [ Sniffles ]
I 'll have to pass that message myself .
Won 't I , hmm ?
Aah !
Uhh !
Lori : Aah !
Ha ha ha !
Aah ! Let go of me !
Aah !
Help ... Me .
Mark !
Ohh !
Aah !
Freddy : Pass on a little message for me , will ya ?
[ Sighs ]
Uh , sheriff , I 've been compiling info
based on eyewitness reports of the hockey mask killer .
We already know who did this .
Sheriff , we closed down the school
and set up a curfew for anyone under 18 .
Good .
Now I want 24 hour roadblocks set up .
Nobody leaves town , nobody gets in .
We 're gonna contain this son of a bitch
before he spreads any further .
Yes , sir .
Sir , shouldn 't we have the FBI come in and- -
no outsiders , Stubbs .
We can handle this . We 've stopped him before .
Ok , I 'm a little lost here .
Stopped who before ?
We don 't say his name out loud .
You 're not from around here .
I don 't expect you to understand .
With all due resect , sheriff ,
I think we have a copycat
of the old Jason Voorhess
crystal lake killer on our hands- -
you listen to me . We do things around here
a certain way for a reason .
And that 's given us 4 years of peace .
So you either do your job and keep your mouth shut
or , so help me God , I will lock you up !
Do you understand me ? !
Do you understand ? !
Yes , sir .
[ Crow caws ]
Charlie : Why don 't we all just leave ?
No , even if we leave ,
Freddy can still get us .
We all know about him , we 're all afraid of him .
It was our fear that gave him his power .
We 're marked now .
Man , screw that clown .
I mean , what kind of a pussy comes
after you in your dreams anyway ?
Now that big ass mother fucker
back at the cornfield ,
all right , that 's who we should be afraid of .
Tell me who the fuck that was .
His name was Jason Voorhess .
Uh , shit , man ... Um ...
How 'd you know we were here ?
Nothing personal , but the Scooby van out back
wasn 't exactly subtle .
And never keep your keys in the door .
Great , so now we 're completely fucked .
No , you 're not .
I 'm here to help you .
Now , this Jason Voorhess supposedly drowned
at camp crystal lake back in 1957
when he was 11 years old .
The counselors weren 't watching him ,
then they made the mistake of killing his mother .
The legend has it that Jason kept returning
from his grave to punish
whoever returned to the camp .
I think we 're dealing with a copycat here .
No . No . No , no , no .
He 's not a copycat .
I 've seen what he can do . He 's the real Jason .
That 's impossible , Linderman . Jason is dead .
Yeah . Well , you 'd better start thinking outside
your little box , dude .
'Cause somebody 's definitely breaking
the fucking reality rules , ok ?
Will : It makes sense in a way .
I mean , what if Freddy brought Jason back
because he was too weak to go after us on his own ,
so he used Jason .
I mean , he knew that we 'd think it was him ,
that we 'd spread the fear again .
And now that it 's working ,
it 's like he can 't shut Jason back down .
Wait a minute . Freddy died by fire ,
Jason by water . How can we use that ?
I think we should concentrate on Jason first .
But I thought we decided
that Freddy was the one pulling the strings .
Shouldn 't we go after him first ?
I don 't know , maybe what we need to do is
to offer Freddy a sacrifice .
Yeah , yeah , totally .
Like a virgin , right ? Someone pure .
Dude , don 't look at me .
Even if you pay for it , it still counts .
Oh , come on .
Look , we all know who the real virgin is here .
Kia ! Come on , Lori .
I know you never made it with will .
Why would he want to
when he can fuck somebody like me ?
[ Chuckles ]
[ Giggles ]
Let 's tie the bitch up .
What ?
Don 't worry , angel .
You 've still got me .
Come on , give daddy a kiss .
Aah !
Your eyes say no-no ,
but my mouth says yes-yes .
Aah !
Aaaaah !
Lori , are you all right ?
You fell asleep .
[ Gasping ]
Ohh !
Oh , shit !
I pulled that out of my dream .
How is that possible ?
Anything is possible now !
God , you just don 't get it !
Oh , God , y 'all , 2 killers ?
We 're not safe awake or asleep .
It 's not the sleep that 's killing us ,
it 's our dreams .
At westin , mark and I never had dreams .
Were you on any drugs ?
Yeah , but there 's something called hypnocil .
They never told us what it was for ,
but everyone there was taking it .
Hypnocil . Experimental drug ...
Not even approved yet by the fda .
Will : Oh , shit .
Used for ...
Suppression of dreams .
We need those pills . Enough for all of us .
Can you get us back to westin hills ?
[ Buzzes ]
[ Monitor beeping ]
All right , this isn 't it , guys .
Come on , let 's go .
[ Whispering ] Hey , dude .
Let 's take a little j-break , huh ?
No , man . He 's a cop .
Oh , come on . What 's he gonna do ,
arrest me ?
Hold up . Hang on a second .
Fuck .
Oh , that 's better .
[ Pounding on door ]
[ Gunshot ]
Where 's freeburg ?
Come on . Come on !
[ Door alarm beeps ]
This is d-wing .
Will : These are the ones who wouldn 't stop dreaming .
Are they dead ?
They 're in a coma .
It says they were given too much hypnocil .
Who would do this to people ?
Your dad 's name is at the bottom
of both of these charts .
[ Coughing ]
Cool ... Yeah .
What the fuck ?
[ Growling ]
[ Laughs ]
Nice .
Oh , yeah . [ Coughs ]
Oh , yeah .
Hold up , man .
What ?
[ Patients whispering ]
What do you want ?
No , I don 't know where the hypnocil is , ok ?
I can 't pour these down the drain .
We need this stuff .
[ Gasps ]
Uhh !
Freeburg !
Freeburg , what are you doing ?
Charlie : We need those drugs !
Dude , no ! Dude- -
aah !
Go on ! Get out of here !
Go !
Ohh !
Aah !
What was that ?
[ Electric crackling ]
Let 's go check it out . Let 's go .
Get back ! Shit ! Hell !
Fucker !
Help me !
Shit ! They 're all empty !
We gotta keep looking .
Maybe there 's some down here .
Damn , it 's gotta be here somewhere .
Aah ! Aah !
Freeburg , come on !
Come on ! Come on !
Kia : What are you waiting for , come on !
Freeburg , time to go .
We gotta go ! Now , come on !
[ Freddy 's voice ] Let me handle this , bitch .
What ?
Come on , come on ! Ok , let 's go !
Will : Let 's go .
No , wait , wait !
Look .
Come to Freddy .
These are my children , Jason .
Go back where you belong !
Ohh !
Fuck you !
Linderman ...
Freddy : These are my children , Jason .
Go back where you belong .
[ Freddy laughing ]
Jason 's mother : Jason ... Jason ...
My special , special boy .
I 'm disappointed in you , Jason .
You disobeyed me .
You were supposed to come back home ,
just kill a few of them !
But I blame myself . I should 've known
you wouldn 't be able to stop killing !
You are like a big , stupid dog
who can 't stop eating ,
even though your master said you 've had enough !
Ha ha ha .
Now it 's time to put this bad dog to sleep ...
For good !
Haaa !
Aah ! Aah !
Freddy : Not my arm !
Aah !
Ha !
[ Chuckles ]
Welcome to my nightmare .
Penny for your thoughts , chief !
Uhh ! Oh , scary .
Ha ha ha ha ha ! Uhh !
Ha !
Ah ha ha ha ha !
Ah ha !
Ha ha ha !
[ Pinball bells dinging ]
[ Alarm buzzes ]
Ha ! Ohh ...
Tilt .
Ahh !
Ah ha ha ha ha !
Why won 't you die ? !
Aah !
Argh !
Aah ! Uhh !
Come on . Come on !
Ahh .
So you are afraid of something
after all , huh ?
Ah ha ha ha ha !
How in the fuck did I let y 'all
talk me into this ?
Why don 't we just try and do it here ?
Why go all the way to crystal lake ?
Lori : Best-case scenario : Jason wins .
He 'll already be home , back where he belongs .
I mean , why follow us anymore ?
And if Freddy wins ?
At least Jason has home-field advantage .
[ Scoffs ]
Ahh .
[ Whimpering ]
[ Chuckles ]
Aww ... How sweet .
[ Shrieks ]
You ugly little shit .
Now there 's a face ...
Only a mother could love !
Ha ha ha ha ha !
Yeah !
Now we 're getting somewhere .
Let 's see what really scares you .
Ohh .
[ Whimpering ]
And dig a little deeper .
Freddy : I 'm dying to see what skeletons
are hidden in your closet .
[ Door creaks ]
Ok , we 're seriously running out of tranq here , guys . Ok ?
I got maybe one dose , plus enough for Lori .
Well , we 're almost there .
Then I better get going .
No , no , just ...
I don 't want you to go .
I 'm coming back .
Just give me 15 minutes , then wake me up .
I 'll bring that bastard Freddy back through .
Just make sure Jason 's waiting for him .
Lori : Now I lay me down to sleep .
[ Oldies song playing on car radio ]
[ Children shouting ]
Children , chanting : Freak show ! Freak show !
Freak show ! Freak show !
Boy : Bull 's-eye !
Children : Freak show ! Freak show ! Freak show !
Try this on !
Ohh !
Children : Freak show ! Freak show ! Freak show !
Stupid !
Ohh ! Ohh !
Aren 't you gonna help the kid ? !
Can 't you see I 'm busy here ?
You mean you 're not coming ?
It 's not my fault this bitch is dead on her feet .
Ha ha ha ha ha !
Aah !
It 's been 5 minutes .
Well , that was the last of the tranq , ok ? We 're out .
Calm down ! Ok ? Just relax !
[ Children shouting ]
Heeeeelp !
Wait ! Give me your hand !
Give me your hand !
Aah !
Help !
Jason ? Aah !
Jason vorhees !
Aah !
[ Freddy laughing ]
Kia : Y 'all ... Y 'all ...
Y 'all , something 's wrong .
It 's like he 's drowning or something .
Freddy must be killing him .
We need him alive !
Dude , what do you want me to do ?
Like , give him mouth-to-mouth or something ?
[ Jason gurgling ]
Um ...
Hell no . Why are you- -
no ! No , I 'm not gonna do that . No !
Kia , look , I would do it myself ,
but I 've had asthma since I was 6 , ok ?
I don 't have the lung power .
No .
Kia , he has asthma !
Ooh ! Ooh ...
Look , you can do this , ok ?
You can do this . You just- -
shut up !
You 're not the one that has to do this .
I know , but I- -
shut up !
Aah !
Oh , my God .
Ohh , God !
Oh , man .
Oh , shit . Oh , shit .
[ Gags ]
[ Whimpering ]
Aah ! Aah !
[ Tires screech ]
[ Kia screams ]
You ! Aah !
[ Blades clink ]
[ Watch beeping ]
What 's wrong , Lori ?
Miss your wake-up call ?
Aah !
Hunh !
Wake me up ! I got him ! I got him !
No !
Lori , come on ! Wake up !
Lori , wake up , please !
Look !
Guys , look .
We 're almost there .
Help me . Come on . We gotta get her up .
Come on . Start running . Start running .
Wake me up !
Daddy , don 't !
[ Whimpering ]
[ Gasps ]
Daddy ! No , daddy , don 't !
Freddy ! It was you !
[ Gasps ]
I 've always had a thing
for the whores that live in this house .
Aah !
[ Screaming ]
Lori , wake up !
Oh , shit .
It 's him . He 's here .
Lori , come on ! You gotta wake up !
Uhh ! Uhh ...
Ha ha ha !
Oh , yes .
[ Whimpering ]
Aah !
My God !
Ohh .
Come on , Lori , wake up !
Lori , please . Wake up !
Lori , please . Lori , please .
Aah !
Go ! Go , go , go !
Ohh !
Lori !
Oh , you fuckin asshole !
Goddamn it !
Aah !
Welcome to my world , bitch .
I should warn you , princess ,
the first time tends to get a little ...
[ Blades clink ]
Messy .
[ Chuckles ]
[ Whimpering ]
Yah !
Get away from her !
Gah !
Uhh !
Linderman .
Unh !
Oh ! Oh , no !
Aah !
Ahh !
[ Gasps ]
Die , you little bitch .
Ha ha ha ha !
Uhh !
Ohh !
Aah !
Jesus , Linderman . You- - you 're really hurt .
No . No , no , no . Don 't worry about me .
Just a scratch .
Just go get help , ok ?
What ? You don 't think- -
look , I 'm just gonna rest here a minute .
Linderman- - I 'm fine , Kia .
Really . Now get out of here .
Go get help . But you- -
just go .
Ok , ok , but ... I 'm gonna be back
as soon as I can .
[ Both coughing ]
Lori !
Think you 're so smart , huh , bitch ?
Freddy !
How sweet ...
Dark meat .
No ! Kia ! Let 's go !
Nooo !
So you 're the one everyone 's afraid of ?
Tell me something .
What kind of faggot
runs around in a Christmas sweater ?
[ Hisses ]
I mean , come on . Get real .
You 're not even scary .
And let 's talk about the butter knives .
What is with the butter knives ?
You trying to compensate for something ?
Maybe coming up a little short there
between the legs , Mr. Krueger ?
Hmm .
I mean , you got
these teensy-weensy little things ,
and Jason has got this big ol ' thing
that 's like ...
Ohh .
Lori : Kia !
No ! No ! Come on !
Come on , Lori . Let 's go .
We can 't help her anymore .
No ! I 'm staying !
Are you crazy ?
You got what you wanted . You pulled Freddy out ,
and now he 's fighting Jason .
Come on ! What more do you want ?
He killed my mother , Will !
It was Freddy .
My dad covered it up to protect me .
He didn 't do it .
Look , he has taken everything from us !
He has ruined both of our pasts- -
and I am not leaving until I see him die !
Uhh ! Unh ! Uhh !
Aah !
Freddy : Man the torpedoes .
Hey , asshole !
Up here !
Aha !
Ahh !
Yeah .
Ah , give me a break .
Uhh !
Ohh ! Ahh ! Aah !
Ohh ! Ohh !
Aah ! Aah ! Aah ! Aah ! Ohh !
Oh , no .
Ohh , noooo !
Ahh !
[ Chuckles ]
[ Groaning ]
Oh ! Aah !
Ohh !
Lori , get the tanks !
Give it up !
Freddy !
Go to hell !
Ohh !
Gah !
Ohh ...
Uhh !
[ Gagging ]
Argh !
Ahh !
[ Spluttering ]
[ Choking ]
It 's ok . It 's ok .
Aah !
You ... Ohh !
Aah ! Aah !
[ Whimpering ]
Ohh !
Welcome to my world , bitch !
[ Freddy laughing ]
[ Hard rock music playing ]